Suku le Suku le Suku le [screaming sound]
Ray what were you doing near my bus?
You will have to play the game.
Hey brother, what happened, is the bus not starting
?  Oh yes friend brother, I don't know
what happened.  It was on a while ago.
Brother, if you say so, I will fix it.  My
grandfather was also a mechanic.  I am also a mechanic
and my son is also a mechanic.  Hey,
what's the matter, brother?  Your family is
mechanics, so do it.  Ok.
Wait 2 minutes.  I will do it now.
[screaming sound]
Hey, it will be fun.
Why brother, is it happening or not?
Start.  Hey brother, I am not moving forward.
Brother, I am not able to push.
Do one thing systematically.  You are
fat by the way.  You push.  I sit on the seat.
Oh yes friend, you said the right thing.   No no no,
something is wrong here.   There
must be some problem.   Wait a minute.  Be
patient.
[Music]
Hey brother, if it's done then stop it, stop it [Laughter]
Son, it's happened, the
bastard has cheated you.